tradeinn.com 2018-02-22

# Tradeinn

1\. LEGAL INFORMATION

**Website:** www.tradeinn.com

 **Company that owns:** Tradeinn Retail Services S.L.

 **Company Adress:** C/ Pirineus, 9, 17460 Celrà (Girona), Spain. 

**Managing Director:** David Martin Gaya 

**Commercial Register:** Registre mercantil de Girona - tomo 1123 / folio 108 / hoja GI20086 - Inscripción 1ª

 **VAT identification number:** ESB17527524

 **Legally responsible for the content of this website:** David Martin Gaya

2\. PRIVACY POLICY

Tradeinn is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully. We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and secondly to provide you with the best service possible. We will not email you in the future unless you have given us your consent. We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us in the future. The type of information we will collect about you when you place an order or register on our Websites includes: Address, Phone Number, Email Address. This information is already stored on our internal systems and our Websites simply verifies you as a customer of Tradeinn. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly. The personal information that we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. We will not transfer or sell your information. We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our Websites. If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should email us at lopd@tradeinn.com.

We use the information you provide for the following purposes:

\- To send updates regarding the status of your enquiry or order.

\- To send newsletters, offers and promotions, you have indicated that you do not object to being contacted for the purposes.

When you place an order we need to know your name, email address and delivery address. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of the status of your request. We may also ask for your telephone number which enables us to contact you urgently if there is a problem with your order.

By submitting information to Tradeinn you consent to the collection and use of this information by Tradeinn. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

We have designer our Websites to protect the information we collect online from unauthorized access. We safeguard your private information by implementing the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedure necessary to protect your privacy. To further protect your security, we also take the reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to your personal profile or making data changes. We are committed to protecting your privacy and have security measures in place to prevent unauthorized access to and disclosure of your personal information.

Newsletter Subscription: your e-mail address will be used for our own marketing purposes until you unsubscribe. It is possible to unsubscribe at any time. If you do not wish to receive information about our products or services you can unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscribe link, which exists at the top of all marketing emails sent by us.

3\. COPYRIGHT

Tradeinn Group has exclusive rights over the entire content and the use of the our stores website, graphics, images, texts, logos, GIFs and icons with the exception of trademarks, logos or content relating to shops or listed products. All reproduction, distribution, modification, retransmission or publication of these elements is strictly forbidden without the prior written accord of the company Tradeinn Group.

4\. COOKIES

\- What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer when visiting a website. This text file stores information that can be read by the website when visiting it again at a later date. Some of these cookies are necessary because otherwise the site is unable to function properly. Other cookies are convenient for the visitor: they remember your username in a secure way as well as your language preferences, for example. Cookies mean that you do not need to fill out the same information each time you visit a website.

\- Why does Tradeinn use cookies?

Tradeinn uses cookies to help us provide you with a better user experience tailored to your personal preferences. By using cookies Tradeinn makes sure that you do not receive or need to enter the same information every single time you visit the Tradeinn websites. Cookies are also used to optimise the performance of the websites. For example, cookies make the checkout process easier or help you to find a specific item of clothing faster.

The list below provides more details about what cookies we use:

\- PHPSESSID, SERVERID, _atuvc, barra_cookies, cookie_cart, cookie_cart_total, shipping data, nospeeder and tradenewsletter: These cookies are needed for the site to work. Without them you won't be able to add items to your basket or checkout.

\- Google Analytics cookies:_utma, _utmb, _utmc y _utmz: These cookies help us understand how people use the site to help us improve it. Google Analytics uses ""cookies"", which are text files placed on your browser, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

\- countryCode, currencyCode, languageCode: These cookies remember your preferences such as language and currency and make it easier to find your recently viewed products. 

\- How can I disable cookies?

You can modify your browser to turn off cookies. This is very easy to do. Please note: if you disable cookies, your user name and password will no longer be stored on any website. Depending on which web browser you use it is possible to control how cookies are used, or to delete existing cookies from your computer. You can find instructions on how to control the use of cookies, or delete cookies from your computer at http://www.aboutcookies.org (English only).

Firefox:

1\. Open Firefox.  
2\. At the top of the Firefox window, click on the ‘Firefox’ button and then select ‘Options’.  
3\. Select the ‘Privacy’ panel.  
4\. Set ‘Firefox will:’ to ‘Use custom settings for history’. Uncheck ‘Accept cookies from sites’ to disable cookies.  
5\. Click ‘OK’ to close the Options window.

Internet Explorer:

1\. Open Internet Explorer.  
2\. Click the ‘Tools’ button, and then click ‘Internet Options’.  
3\. Click the ‘Privacy’ tab, and then, under ‘Settings’ move the slider to the top to block all cookies, and then click ‘OK’.

Google Chrome:

1\. Open Google Chrome.  
2\. Click on the tool icon.  
3\. Select Settings’.  
4\. Near the bottom of the page, click ‘Show advanced settings’.  
5\. In the ‘Privacy’ section, click ‘Content settings’.  
6\. To disable cookies, select ‘Block sites from setting any data’.

Safari:

1\. Open Safari.  
2\. Choose ‘Preferences’ in the toolbar and then click ‘Privacy’ (You can find the tool bar which looks like a gearwheel, above and on the right in the Safari window.)  
3\. In the ‘Block cookies’ section, you can specify if and when Safari should accept cookies from websites To see an explanation of the options, click the Help button (question mark)  
4\. If you want to see which websites store cookies on your computer, click Details.

Please remember that if you delete or restrict cookies from the Tradeinn websites you may not be able to experience the full benefit of some of the features and services a website has to offer.

5\. FACEBOOK SOCIAL PLUGINS

Our website uses social plugins ( "Plugins") of the facebook.com social network, which is operated by the Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The plugins are marked with a Facebook logo or with the words "Facebook social Plugin".

If you visit one of our websites, which contains such a plugin, your internet browser connects directly to the servers of Facebook. The content of the Plugin is transferred directly to your browser and is integrated to the website.

By integrating the plugin, Facebook receives the information that a corresponding website of ours has been viewed. If you are logged into Facebook, Facebook can assign your visit to your account. If you interact with the plugins, for example you confirm the "Like" button or make a comment, the corresponding information from your browser is sent directly to Facebook and saved there as well.To find out the purpose and extent of the collection of data, the further processing and usage of your data by Facebook as well as your rights and possible settings in this regard to protect your privacy please consider the privacy statement of Facebook.
